basis
umare
bla
voodoo
t echoes
Luciano
dameda mayakimitaidane
oishiiatta torotororo
mamanosuupumatsuteruyo
samishiitoki furooren
waraitaitoki sunifutomi
komatsutatoki sunafukin
tayorigaiaru papatomama
saa hajimaritamuuninguda
nee watashitoasobe asobe
saa anatakaramuuninguda
nee watashi hireindesho haha
ponpinponpiporinshamyororinko
watashimoanatamorun.tatta
run.run.tatta run.run.tatta run.tatta
dameda
If you are going to go right now, you should get to the island.
What if the water rises when we are halfway?
Nepsu, it doesn't work so fast. We are going back on the journey in good time.
But how do we know what's in good time?
Do not, murdered. When it's time to come back, I will let you know a decent bun with PUM.
You even hear it there on a distant beach.
Is it quite strong?
Hi then!
Have fun!
Take care of my sister!
fool! I can take care of myself.
Too difficult.
Nepsu, come already!
What about you?
I'm absolutely worried.
haa ...
What's wrong with you? Now you are not worried.
What if the tide is still rolling in our neck?
Do you like a stupid life jacket?
The rising water follows the moon, and you never know where it is on the way.
Nepsu, you are incredible! Are you not interested in the Aare Bear buried on the island?
ooo, aare?
did not hear or?
oops ...
Oh a round island!
I know. The water has already fallen. Let's race on the island. Y, ka, ku, ny!
Muvi, Pekko, you stole.
I'm not even yeah!
It's a rook!
Don't laugh at me!
ai ...
Pekko?
Oh, you look at how Somi saw and I found.
Yeah, they are beautiful. Especially that shoe.
Then you get it.
Oh, please.
Ah, cheer, I asked it.
Look, nipple, real octopus.
Yeah.
Nipsu, what do you stand there for it?
I watch the sea so that it doesn't slip into our neck.
You're nothing about it in these, idiat.
I'm going to look for a better observation place.
Nipsu!
Stay!
here at least I can't see anything.
Ah, I see in the rock in every direction.
Kallio departure.
heavy stones.
oops.
haa, real amethysts.
Where am I?
oh.
haa.
oh how beautiful and valuable.
and how much.
haa.
Happiness.
I got it.
Aaaaa!
butter.
Do you think these are a little enough?
Yeah, thank you.
What are you doing?
Don't you see? We build a hut. Come and help.
The hut is too small for all of us what the officials have.
strange, I haven't seen nips at all.
Nothing. It's quite peaceful.
Let's go nipsua.
strange. Hoi Nipsu.
Nipsuu.
He has left home alone.
not. He would have said. Nipsu, Hoi, where are you?
came with rain.
about.
The clock is now uniform.
aha.
I want to see how it works.
It works well. I have designed it to launch my aircraft.
Well, block your ear.
hmm.
block your ear.
oops.
Niisku.
I did not take the rain in mind.
Nipsuu.
Nipsuu, where are you?
You come here.
Where has he faded?
The water has begun to rise again.
Oops, help, help, boom truck!
Water has entered.
aha.
I have found an amethyst cave.
What a lucky kick.
It is more companion than a treasure chest.
oops.
How did I get out of here?
Boum troll!
Oh! Help, help!
I would have thought the nipple knows that the gun will get wet in Satella.
I didn't expect rain. Let's keep busy and have time to have the island.
is currently in full moon and high tide is particularly high.
miserable!
Nipsuu!
Nipsuu! Where are you?
Listen!
Have you found a nipple?
The water is so high that we can get back.
What?
We are in Uka.
Good gentleman Väkin!
Niisku would like to bump when we have time to return.
But the sea is going to us.
The construction of the cabin was not a crazy idea after all.
Nipsu must be found.
Yes.
Nipsuu!
water flows.
If the water gets in, I'll get out.
Umi, we cannot get to the island during high tide.
We need to come up with something else.
We get to the island.
Only rushes.
Moomin Bapp, nothing will come.
You come up with something?
The current seems to increase.
Cave mouth, rescue.
Amethyst!
Moomintroll, come and help!
I think it sounded like a nipple sound.
I didn't hear.
Moomintroll!
Nipsu, where are you?
Moomintroll, help!
Moomintroll, Come and help!
The sound comes from the cave.
Nipsu!
How have we got there?
It's not important. Help out!
to get your stops.
What are you doing?
Tentuu.
The books have experience.
I am starving.
Did you have something to bite in the snack basket?
stayed. Leave the scraps by a campfire.
The Moomintroll has first made fire.
finally sells to collect dry leaves.
clear. Nipsu, you will help me?
and not. I will return to the cave to get more amethytes.
There is no time for it. You help or I eat your part.
Even so.
him!
Is there anything about it?
Well, no.
I have wanted.
Is there anything about it?
surely.
According to my calculations, I was able to fly here to the island.
When I get to the island, I pull the boat there.
The plan cannot fail to swear by it.
Good.
Now I'm leaving.
Continue, continue!
Crash the wings!
on Piemälä Island.
This works as I am planned.
If I have not misjudged my own forces.
Good.
I have reached the island.
tel!
Don't be pampered, niisku!
Don't fall!
Don't Wood ...
Help!
Niisku, are you okay?
Yes ... I guess.
Thanks to the help, Muikkunen.
can't stand what you are flying here in the middle of the night.
The Moomintroll and partners are on the island in their own Onnesa ditch.
by water.
We have tried to save them without success.
Oh in that way.
Wait in peace for the next low water.
I am sure they will find some rain protection.
hopefully.
It's not cold now.
They have previously spent the night under the bare sky.
Well, so.
Stocky tuned water.
hmm ... Nous, Muikkunen.
What are you moving?
I came to see the round island.
Incredible, you can see.
In the event that the fog is a little blurred.
What sound was it?
somewhere rolled over.
The roar is roaring!
And no sound is under the ground.
크게
What was it?
The country was shy.
Do you shy?
Well, Pekka!
The sound comes from here.
Don't go there, you have to danger.
Wait for me.
The sound is near.
Hattuots.
Hattavatit competes. They have fun.
What was it?
oh!
oh! We are going to sleep.
What about Hattivat?
have certainly left.
The water drops.
We get home. Hurrah!
oops!
snus Muikkunen!
Muikkunen!
Father!
and nap!
Dad doesn't wake up!
NIisku, what is you?
is! Now it's morning!
Moomintroll!
sister, why are you here?
Moomintroll, is all well?
You didn't cold in the rain?
Of course I don't.
Yeah, blow. I brought you beautiful shoes.
Thank you.
look at this.
What a beautiful one. Amethyst right?
That's right. I had many amethysts, but they fell into the water.
Sometimes we start to get them.
and we see something extraordinarily beautiful on the island.
Share. Let's go home. Mamma is definitely worried.
Let's leave!
What? What?
Stay after!
Moomintroll, you are cold.
And you look tired, good police officer.
Let's go for a drink. You too, naisku.
Yeah.
Thank you.
pokettoniakogarewo ippaitsumetedekakeyou
hoonikaze sayasayato hikarihaodoruyo
kanarazutegamikakuyo hanabirakitsutehari
meniutsurukeshikinokotoya deatsutaninnokoto
dakarazuttobokunokoto wasurenaidene
sonnakotokangaete yagateyumenonakahe
itsukakitto itsukakitto itsukasutekinatabinideyou