medamayakikimitaidane oishiiattatorotororo
mamanosuupumatsuteruyo
samishiitokifuroren waraitaitokisunifutomi
komatsutatokisunafukin tayorigaiarupapatomama
saahajimaritamuuninguda neewatashitoasobeasobe
saaanatakaramuuninguda neewatashikireidesho
ponpinponpikorinshamyororinko watashimoanatamoruntatta
runruntattarunruntattaruntatta
Today is still there.
Do you carry a bag between?
It's not heavy.
Thank you. We get to the point and there we can rest.
Do you remember the tighter and the nuance with king's ruby?
They have returned to the Moomin Valley with their suitcase.
There is smoke from the Moomin House barrel.
Good, mummamma cooks for dinner.
Moomins are so nice.
They will break our print.
when we have such a wonderful gift for them.
Yeah, I'm sure the Moomins will scream for joy when you see it.
Do you continue your journey?
Yeah.
I now carry my suitcase.
Yes I still can.
oh, from KuPS. Sorry, lighter than I imagined.
The bag is in ...
I know, gift for me.
didn't, there is a gift for the Moomins.
They have houseworking stuff, they don't need anything.
The suitcase is ours.
count it in the world. Thanks.
We want a gift for the Moomins even if they don't need.
What to do now, Navy?
I don't know.
Does that Kelmi live here?
I don't know, I don't see this last time.
What's the advice?
This misery is locked.
Disifestly!
Why should everything be locked?
I want to open the suitcase.
River a small object there is.
But a little object can be thematic.
opened.
What is this?
looks like a tulip onion.
True.
A little different anyway.
You?
Whatever the suitcase it is.
Well mine. What are you right?
Why didn't you open your suitcase?
I was watching you.
as a lust.
or so.
Do you mean that you locked the bag?
Of course I mean.
Do you consider me crazy?
Where does that suitcase come from?
Say.
You have stolen your suitcase.
And I'm not.
I found it from the ground.
Only this onion had.
important.
Stink not.
He can't eat it.
Own.
It's not the tulip onion.
What's the strange thing?
I donate you the whole onion and suitcase.
Welcome.
Hi, Teikko.
fun to see.
for a long time.
say anything else.
Come in now.
does not stay here at the stairs.
The most, ultimate.
Father guests.
A very good day.
New week.
Welcome.
Good day.
What a hustle and bustle.
Tiuhti and Viuhti.
You have not been seen at times.
Moominpappa, we bring you a very wonderful gift.
It would not have been necessary.
You are always welcome.
Moominmamma, we come up with a great gift for you.
Goodbye. Thanks.
Do you like our gift?
Of course I like.
What is that gift?
I'm pretty excited.
Oh miserable, sorry.
The gift was stolen on the way.
stolen?
It was such an extremely fun gift.
I would have certainly liked your gift.
How sad?
I would have liked to see it.
Moominmamma, Can we visit your nature?
Even though we don't have expensive.
Of course, stay for as long as you want.
Did you hear, Viutti?
I heard and I'm happy.
Thank you, Moominmamma.
Please tell me more about where the gift was stolen from you.
here near.
in the Moomin Valley?
That's right. It was stolen in the soil.
There are not many thieves in these corners.
Not that way.
and the one I know.
Stink!
No stink!
Stinky shark!
Stink!
Don't bother.
You can see that you were currently in Nokos.
Give the goods you stole from our guests.
Your guests? Oh from them.
aha, you stole.
I don't know what you are talking about.
You stole a wonderful gift from our guests.
Give it here.
Give it back before I get angry or I against the consequences.
so calm down.
Own troll, what did you say?
Give it a gift.
Do you talk about some ideal gift?
I spoke. How?
Wonderful gift.
This is just ...
When you laugh.
Ihihi!
ahaa. Now it became clear from whom the stolen has stolen the suitcase.
The gift is not lost.
No, but it's no longer here.
Where is it?
I took it to Hemul to investigate which plant the tuber it is.
I also took a suitcase.
or the gift is tuber.
So some onion.
That's right.
It looked like a tulip onion, but I don't really think that's it.
I came that a wonderful gift is an old onion.
It can be a very rare plant onion.
Hemuli couldn't know it.
I wish the gift would have been another ruby.
ruby?
Oh yeah. After all, the fan had stolen a ruby ​​from Mörö and hid it in a suitcase.
air, the bag was familiar.
Have you stolen the onion?
How do you know?
Let's go see what Hemuli is doing.
Hemuli!
Grow, good day.
Is that onion I brought yesterday?
Void looking.
I'm just planting it.
Which plant is it?
No dream. I've never seen the same thing.
Then it must be a rare plant onion.
I am a little worried.
What?
The onion is damaged. Hopefully the schools it experienced will not prevent it from germinating.
Ah, now I remember. The stink tried to taste the onion.
It's a villain!
Hi Hemuli, don't plant onions yet.
oh, why not?
Let's take the onion to the one for whom it is intended.
about.
Here comes water!
Well, is this?
Visit, please.
Tiuhti and Viuhti, now tell us what plant it is?
controlled from elite.
Good, look when ...
Wait, Tiuhti!
What now, Viuhti?
Well, when I want to tell the whole story.
So well, what's up?
Better, of course, that you tell.
Tell me already.
Look when we start from the beginning so the onion is not from here at all.
The onion comes from somewhere very far, even farther than the moon.
Good to meet.
And therefore it is less common than any other onion and great gift for our friends for us.
Unique onion.
And the most unique is that it starts to sing.
I guess.
Yes, the flower sings very well, it has a good voice.
Sorry, just continue.
and it sings special songs.
Thanks to the botany.
But maybe it's good that not all flowers sing.
Where did you find the onion?
Would I tell you?
Same.
After all, we are not forbidden.
Tell me by wonder. Who did you get onion unless you come from space?
no magician.
Of course.
The magician liked the onion, but even more ruby.
We did barter.
The magician already had a ruby, but he apparently wanted it. That's what.
But you are happy to give him up from ruby.
We had had it for a long time and were sure we should be singing the flower.
It is clear.
was good.
We had a lot of trouble when we were last in the Moomin House.
We are in great dedication.
We made our mind come again.
fun to hear. Thanks.
I felt that the onion would already be a wise to learn the water bowl.
It is sure to be.
We monitor its development.
and when it bursts into the flower, it starts with a launa.
Just next to the note.
How soon that flower.
in two days.
Well the sky.
Let it suddenly put it in the water.
you.
Good.
I immerse the onion.
Only two days.
Bum papa, can you stay here?
You can of course.
I too will be left.
Two days had passed.
and then three.
and soon a full week.
But the onion was quite like.
Ten days had passed.
and the onion looked as lifeless as before.
I speak.
Visits went for a walk.
I almost believed I could see the song but anyone.
maybe the onion has received too much moisture.
It is very possible, mom.
The bite of the smell did not do it good.
Witch is our only chance.
But dangerous.
I don't like this at all.
We've got lost.
Tilti!
Come on! Come on!
did not go.
Don't worry.
Help! Tilti was aquered.
Help! Help! Come and save your tilt!
Tilti!
So you can't do it.
Unfortunately not.
Grandma could make the onion germinate, but I probably can't.
Looking at when I haven't completely learned the witch yet.
When will your grandmother come back home?
Not for a short time.
I wouldn't run here by the way.
What are you now?
There is hot drink here.
Yes, I can.
What did you say?
Yes, it grows into a real singing flower.
grow and it sings beautifully.
Believe me.
Hi TIHTI.
I am sure that one day, the onion will still germinate.
It would be fun to hear anyone singing.
Everybody has given up to hope for the hope that the onion would grow a singing flower.
Hemulik, who was so excited about the gift of Tiuhdi and Navy.
Why not germinate?
Do you see signs of germination?
Not visible.
Did you stop watching?
I quit. Hard to observe when there is nothing to observe.
It came to mind here.
What?
I've heard that some people call plants.
that they would grow better and it really helps.
so reportedly. Unscientific, though.
If you tried, and what would the music fit on the bulb?
If it grows into a singing flower, you would think that any music will bring life to it.
Yeah, of course. Great!
sniffing, come already!
and don't just sit in it. We have a job.
But Hemuli!
Without you, nothing will come from this.
What sound is it?
sniffing gummy plays a harmonica on the onion.
What's the miracle?
I don't know.
I suppose we should gradually end the visit? Our gift was a completely wolf.
Not that useful.
Well, that's what it looks like.
Would you like a cup of tea?
Ah, yes thank you.
Good idea.
Why didn't call?
The onion should be spent on the onion!
The pain of it is effective.
already!
Well now what was it?
useless that onion to lame it so that it does not germinate.
sshh! Shut up.
I hear something.
What?
Onion this!
It grows.
Mummamma!
mummy!
The singing flower has germinated.
It has leaves!
Did the lip got my harp at that time?
Incredible ta.
How can you go to you?
Be crazy too.
It really looks like it could sing.
You were right.
That's what we said.
nice plant.
Very nice.
Sorry to doubt.
seemed so incredible.
Grandma would be amazed at this.
I hear.
When you sleep, you get hungry.
New album.
Good appetite.
Hemuli planted the honor of the singing flower.
But still far enough from his house, it would not control him.
Thank you.
pokettoniakogarewo ippaitsumetedekakeyou
hoonikaze sayasayato hikarihaodoruyo
kanarazutegamikakuyo hanabirakitsutehari
meniutsurukeshikinokotoya deatsutaninnokoto
dakarazuttobokunokoto wasurenaidene
sonnakotokangaete yagateyumenonakahe
itsukakitto itsukakitto itsukasutekinatabinideyou