medamayakikimitaidane oishiiattatorotororo
mamanosuupumatsuteruyo
samishiitokifuroren waraitaitokisunifutomi
komatsutatokisunafukin tayorigaiarupapatomama
saahajimaritamuuninguda neewatashitoasondeasonde
saaanatakaramuuninguda neewatashikireidesho
ponpinponpikorinshamyororinko watashimoanatamoruntatta
runruntattarunruntattaruntatta
A rest
The rest of the valley seemed to reach hard.
Our hero had drifted to the islands, after all, did not offer a safe harbor.
new dangers. Hazards? What happens to our hero?
The islands have a volcano and discharges and the whole island flies to the sky.
But then the hero's story is over.
This is cold.
I should have closed the window when Tuomainen's storm is raging.
of course a terrible storm coming.
Good storm. This is fun to write.
about.
Don't go out for a long time.
I can't blow as big as you.
It will not work with a straw pill.
Beautiful. Just like snow.
I'll get more.
You can't. They are mine.
You races nicely.
I also want to hang out the snow series.
Hi, Moomintroll.
What?
Sorry for intervening to play.
But could you be a little quieter?
I try to focus on writing.
Yeah. Thanks.
What to do?
This can be done quietly. Let's go out.
Wind. I just came up with a new play.
Celebration!
This is how it is flown.
I suspect we are too heavy.
This is a little mill.
could have a pool. I come to the fire.
Niippu, you didn't happen.
This is a boring play.
Celebration!
Where the little one is selling now.
This is coming.
I?
No, I am ...
Help!
Hi, hey, hey.
did not happen.
Oh Saint Sylvi.
Hi Sell!
Look.
Is there someone at home?
Here at the top, Moomin mirror.
What's the case, so muli?
I'm repairing when Little My Sell landed on my neck.
ahaa.
Rocket will be destroyed here.
But not. Nearly as much.
Hi, don't wolf useless.
We will repair the teddy bear of the houses.
like that?
or what?
fun. I've never built anything.
Your house is better than a new one.
I don't know.
We should paint the entire house in bright colors.
as it seems gloomy.
I have paint at home. Let's start to get tools right away.
We will soon be back.
Area is there any ability?
The wind calmed down.
and I finally get to spread the laundry.
What a pleasure to drink day coffee on the porch.
Pappa gold, how's your book progress?
That's it.
me, dad!
I borrow us with wheelbarrows.
and saw and hammer.
What's in it?
Search for board pieces from the basement.
clear.
Nipsu! Today is not done and not playing.
I'm not playing.
What are you doing with mopes?
Paint the walls.
Paint?
Don't be restless.
We return to food.
Moomintroll, what are you going to?
We are now going to repair Hemul's house.
AI!
Hello then!
I look for a goal.
Nipsu, Anna Board.
As long as I go.
O Nipsu, Ressu.
Do you need help?
No thanks, I can.
O.
Give me between me.
No!
Give the same.
Don't mess up my thoughts.
Good, good.
Nipsu, speed!
Don't look.
Let's see what you did.
This is not so dangerous.
Return to Lapland and immediately.
Oh heaven.
You are not your way.
Go to collect the plant.
Everything here is in control.
that ...
I will not be happy to leave my house on their desire.
The following week, Hemuli lived in the Moomin House.
The Moomintroll and its partners were up to her house while.
Moomin.
mummamma and mummy.
kas memmel?
Days.
Do you also go to the hemulil?
We are.
The house is reportedly ready.
I heard that the little night was dumb.
My house ento.
You would let him be painted.
Well why not?
me and dad!
Hi Moomintroll!
Good work must be granted.
so I do.
Let's go inside.
Oio.
Joas.
A little enough for the old person.
No, no, excellent botanist.
Yes, just beautiful.
Do you think?
Hemuli and you don't like the result?
I like. It's unusual.
In the mornings you can get your eyes as soon as you open to the plant knowledge.
May I cinnamon you hemuli.
It's fun to hear.
The room can inspire you to do something fine weak.
fine.
You can dream of new plants.
You do not think scientifically.
hehehehe.
butter.
Share.
hehehehe.
in a good way.
I don't feel bad for me.
From tonight, Hemul was bothered by a strange sleep.
Where am I?
I have seen flowers before. New species.
oh, oh, oh, oh.
Professor Hemuli and I haven't found a new plant?
Else.
A lovely room should inspire you to revolutionize discoveries.
Listen, there are not so many new plants.
How do you know if they have not been found?
cannot be many.
Find even one, Professor Hemuli.
The Vuone helps you find.
Professor Hemuli.
Stop, stop already.
Stop, no.
It was just a dream.
Professor Hemuli.
Let me be.
terrible, I can't sleep in my house.
All here is fine.
oh, oh, oh.
Hemuli.
Bike, from the police.
Why are you up this time?
Only a small walk before I go again.
Oh heaven.
Good night.
Walking nightgown on.
What are you playing today?
Let's think.
I know.
I'm not going to fly on an umbrella.
fool, not even wind today.
I thought we would continue to renovate Hemul's house.
Good idea.
Also painted outside the house.
Do you immediately put on?
What's it?
Hemuli.
Hemuli, Hemuli.
day but.
Why do you sleep here?
I saw such horrible dreams in my room.
I kept walking and then I started to sleep.
If you sleep, sleep in beautiful rooms.
That's right.
We were just coming to see how your house can handle.
We have also decided to paint your house from outside.
Don't come to paint.
Why not?
You have already done enough.
Don't think I can get to the house bouquet.
Go play.
now home.
It was strange to use from Hemul.
Well, so do we.
Moomin -troll, you said that Hemuli horti at night press.
I just met the police champion and said he had seen Hemul in the woods on a nightgown.
Hemuli had seemed very sleepy.
Does Ressukka suffer from insomnia?
Don't be injured, Moomin -troll, but maybe Hemuli has not adapted to new colors in her home.
The Hemuliha was very pleased.
at least he said so and the walls herself in recession.
So yes.
No, no, stop, don't!
No, there is nothing to sleep.
oh, Hemuli.
Are you fish now?
I don't, no sint. Fish can sleep.
happy fish.
Well, good night, a believer.
Good night.
Ah, you saw Hemul?
like that, and he seemed terribly tired.
maybe Dad was right after all.
You should ask Hemulio yourself.
Niai. If Hemuli is unable to sleep because of our paintings, something must be done.
Hemuli, do you hide something from us?
that I was secret from you something impossible.
You look terrifying tired.
I also tired. Look at it.
oh, I'm careful.
This is nothing. I was peak when I got up too suddenly.
If you can't sleep at home, that is, because of the walls.
The painting easily goes into a former color.
oh, no, no, no. You need to.
After all, I can sleep first at night.
oh, can't.
Isn't that?
cannot.
It does not.
It doesn't get.
Is it?
Don't get.
Sorry to penetrate home.
I don't do it for another.
Hi, Pölle.
Be happy when you can monitor all night without feeling tired.
oh, oh, oh.
Not to sleep.
Where does that look come from?
Oh heaven, oh heaven, can life.
oh that still flowers.
Moomintroll, Moomintroll.
oh, Hemuli.
up, up, right up.
Moomin Pappa, wake up, wake up.
Wake -up, Moomin mom.
AI, Hemuli.
What has happened?
Come and not.
Come and it is not.
Look.
I haven't seen anything as beautiful.
what flowers.
Nothing when the forest dark.
and they bloom only at the center.
so no one has seen them.
After all, you have found a new sport.
So I am.
I have made a great discovery.
Great, your celebrity only increases.
Congratulations.
Hemuli, I'm happy for you.
Departure has found.
Muni and partners have honor.
What?
Elet would have painted in my house and took a night's sleep.
I wouldn't have found flowers.
I'm playing gratitude.
To be honest I.
Well that's it. The matter has been dealt with.
ice mamma, will tomorrow a big party will be held in honor of Hemul's discovery?
Good idea.
Let's get into bed to get up to get up to prepare.
Thank you.
Pull you like you to sleep.
I will be here to make observations.
know even if the flowers disappear, for example, in the morning.
What's found?
Suddenly painted the only one.
Hope Hemuli is now surprised.
What is that Äliina?
Let's see it.
No Hemuli will come.
Good morning Hemuli.
We paint all the surfaces into a former color.
You can sleep properly again.
may what have you seen?
Stop painting immediately.
Try to paint my bedroom again.
I like it and now I fall into the shit.
That way, Hemuli learned to keep his variegated room.
He slept well again, but sometimes went for a walk at night.
You don't know what you can find at night.
he is still still.
You can find at night.
pokettoniakogarewo ippaitsumetedekakeyou
hoonikaze sayasayato hikarihaodoruyo
kanarazutegamikakuyo hanabirakitsutehari
meniutsurukeshikinokotoya deatsutaninnokoto
dakarazuttobokunokoto wasurenaidene
sonnakotokangaete yagateyumenonakahe
itsukakitto itsukakitto itsukasutekinatabinideyou