shibuyasato Mercy
fuu。
Seems to Laff 쉽shou
raamenha bokata
none
ohisamakarakonnichiha horamedamayakikimitaidane
oishiiattatorotororo mamanosuupumatsuteruyo
samishiitokifurooren waraitaitokisunipputo
mikomattatokisunafukin tayorigaiarupapatomama
saahajimaridamuuminda neewatashitoasobeasobe
saaanatakaramuuminda neewatashikireindesho
ponpinponpiporinshamyororinko watashimoanatamorunkatta
runrunkattarunrunkattarunkatta
sparked
One of the plot of a momake is a marking sleep
Where have I got?
plunge forward, forward ...
Behind the waterfall you will find what you are looking for.
I'm not looking for anything.
Behind the waterfall.
What can I find there?
got.
Aaaaaah!
Well, it was an impressive sleep.
was. I have often dreamed that I fall or fly, but I have never happened to me in a dream that I was looking for something.
Are you sure to find?
I've been thinking a lot about it, but I'm not looking for anything.
ahaa. Have you seen that waterfall?
Well I'm not. Hi, I have heard.
Who has told about it?
You.
I?
After all, it exists?
You said it is in lonely mountains.
Oh, take me there. Sleep is bothering me so I can't get it.
It was sleep.
Let's go with me.
Aarua, stuffed.
Good.
I am watered.
Then go to bed.
I think I go.
Mom, I'm leaving with Nuuska -Muikkunen in the morning.
Let's go.
with Muikkunen on an excursion to the lonely mountains.
What, before breakfast?
Yeah, do you pack for us for a snack?
Of course.
Thank you, good night.
Mamma, where did Moomin Pekka said he was going?
for lonely mountains.
Time far.
After all.
So early and so in the car.
Only for a fun trip.
He secretly something.
How?
I don't think he was so tired that he had to go to bed.
oh, don't you?
He has something in mind.
I feel the signs you need excitement.
He may be in trouble.
It's best for me to follow her.
Thank you, mother.
Good morning, snus Muikkunen.
Good morning.
I have a lunch for each of us.
The mother is a pleasure.
Thank you, mother.
The mother is a joy.
Well, wonder.
The Moomintroll is early.
Oops, you flowers anyway.
I didn't expect it at all this year.
I mentioned something fun with you in noiku.
I didn't know it was so far away.
Is it?
Well a little.
rest.
Yes I can. What about you?
I'm a walker.
Fitness deceives.
Straight to follow and stay hidden here.
Row already!
Do you think we'll find something?
I'm not so sure. That was just a dream.
So.
Remote if Mars is out and I say I'm hungry.
I might get something to eat.
No. They could be secured as a nose.
What are the subject looking for?
Something valuable or not?
This is the waterfall I've seen in my dream.
But you really don't know what you should look for.
No idea.
Dreams are remarkable.
walk behind the waterfall and watch a little.
does not look very inviting.
This is the waterfall I've seen in my dream.
Here's a slippery Faro. I look at where you step.
This is where Turkey gets wet.
Now we have come right behind the waterfall.
I don't see anything special.
ahead.
What's that?
What's so?
Green!
Probably emeraldy.
It's beautiful.
Are you looking for emerald in your dream?
I didn't look.
What else would you have been looking for?
There is nothing else here.
After all, such a great emerald is good to look for anyone.
It's terribly large.
know the biggest that exists.
If it were smaller, the lady could like it.
someone screams.
someone screaming at us.
This is a load, makeup and really could be rushed.
over there.
views.
help me!
At least I didn't dream of saving the stink.
He has overshadowed us.
Heaven's stitch, stop slipping and start to help.
As a terrible wound.
Aisuli, we help. Stay in places.
Stay, stay.
This is a larger gemstone.
I don't sleep as good as Moomin, Pekko.
I also.
But I didn't dream of gemstones.
Differently fine.
But of course Hemuli friend we value more of his rare plants.
of course. I wouldn't change them anywhere.
Not even for this rainy stone. As beautiful as it is.
jewels are the best I know.
I agree.
Mom, you get emerald.
Thank you, Moomin Pekko.
I would take the emerald mind well, but you have to keep it.
As your dream became true, you are supposed to keep the emerald.
It's gorgeous, but what can you do with it?
It would be a great letter weight, but I rarely get mail.
Fire rain.
Oh, will it come?
If the children are outdoors, they get wet.
They get wet anyway because they went for a swim.
Now drops.
Do you go to the cave shelter? You are already wet.
I'm dry and I'm going to stay dry.
Little, come. I'll take you to the cave.
ha ha, you dare not go there alone.
I am afraid of very few things, but there is a thunderstorm alone.
in that style.
what's the rain?
Hi, it rains.
AI, AI, AI.
This is too much.
it rains so that it is painful.
Caspin!
All my plant is.
What do I do?
AI, AI, AI.
AI, AI, AI. What a hando.
I rotated to this place.
Raikku passed.
unprecedented granules.
There must have been a lot of bad sheds.
Yes.
Yeah.
Hood Papa, disaster!
granules would knock Hemul.
Oh, abomination.
Hemul is carried here.
I can no longer carry a meter.
Don't always choose.
in the eyes of the dark.
Hemuli!
All ruined past.
Father, the frenzy brought Hemul's flower and greenhouse.
It's horrible.
All my plant, all my lovely flowers are crushed.
Everything is over.
carry Hemuli in.
Speed!
Hood priest, I rotated.
Nipsu, don't exaggerate.
Step at once, nips, yes you can.
Cover Hemuli in.
Carefully count him on the couch.
His hard fever has risen.
about the nerve shock, I'm sure.
Let's go immediately to mix the medicine.
Rocking my plant, all past.
Don't go.
Hardly any more garden can be obtained.
by no means.
We do something, Hemuli does not wish for IKI in the world.
I am sure that the garden can be planted again.
This will not work.
Of course we could plant some species, but Hemuli has collected plants around the world.
Magic is used.
magic?
Could you do something?
I doubt his abilities in this matter.
I have anyone.
I'm sure.
It is useless for me to complain that Hemuli has experienced tough and not to recover.
But you are a witch.
Can't you really do anything for Hemul's garden?
I do not say that it crosses Martini.
But when Hemuli is so depressed you can't get out of bed.
It does not add Martiani.
Let's leave.
hmm.
Moomintroll, a pity that we didn't help.
If you can't do anything so you can't.
The matter will not heal.
There is also a limits for the witch.
I've had to notice it.
It's sad.
Hi then Alisa.
Hello.
O.
ahaa, I come up with.
What did you get?
What do you think, would a magician be able to return the garden to the former?
magician?
Once we were hopeful for anything and the magician fulfilled our wishes.
True, the magician is able to help us.
But how do we find him?
Hi Alisa.
What?
Could you ask your grandmother, does she know how to connect to the magician?
Well and did you know where to find a magician?
apparently. The witch jumped on the bone's back and went looking for him.
Oh, maybe those should already come back.
The magician does not live next door.
We just have to wait.
I'm worried about Hemul.
Don't give, grandma is next to her.
Well, now is better Hemuli Rukka.
From there, that magician comes on the back of the band.
Witch found him!
We need to reward witch.
Hope the magician is well on.
Never, except when he got a royal bubble from Tiudi and Vadi.
You called me.
We desperately need the help of the magician.
I'm not a magician called from any whim.
Of course you are not, we are very sorry that we have to bother you.
No one else can help.
and most recently the magician fulfilled all our wishes.
But you did a great service for me.
I also do not run home visits.
For your service you have already received a reward, even abundant if you allow you to add.
Can we do another service?
You are not.
Don't we?
No, no. Hardly just.
How so?
You brought me a good time, it doesn't happen.
What service could we do?
five of it.
We want to know.
Let it be the past.
With you, I finally got them to King Rubin.
so?
But I'm missing.
The finest of emeralds, Queen emerald.
I don't want to wait 300 years.
emerald, other troll.
Magician, wait.
Why?
succeeds, Queen emerald.
This is it.
Queen emerald, I can't believe this.
Good night.
Good night, my troll.
After this incident, the rest of the other fellows always fell asleep in the hope of a lovely sleep.
But if he had a dream, he didn't remember it anymore in the morning.
Thank you.
pokettoniakogarewo ippaitsumetedekakeyou
hoonikaze sayasayato hikarihaodoruyo
kanarazutegamikakuyo hanabirakitsutehari
meniutsurukeshikinokotoya deatsutaninnokoto
dakarazuttobokunokoto wasurenaidene
sonnakotokangaete yagateyumenonakahe
itsukakitto itsukakitto itsukasutekinatabinideyou